Guide to the Irving S. Olds Collection of Naval and Other Historical Prints and Related Papers 1587-1960 PR 47
New-York Historical Society
- Series II. Prints from the Olds Collection Donated by White & Case, 1761-1894; 2.63 Linear feet in flat files and one flat box
  - Labels from backing of prints, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    The prints donated by White & Case were unframed in 2018. Any labels that were on the backing were retained. Some were kept in the folders with the prints, others were compiled together in this small box with a box.